

#### PROFILE STATEMENT

Mentally Strong, passionate worker specialized in GIS. Sacrificing and cooperative with strong communication skill. Bilingual in Korean and English. Certificates in GIS and Microsoft Office programs. 120+hours of volunteer service and 2 years of service in the Korean Air force. Flexible and adaptable to work in changing environment.

# **EDUCATION**

# Master of Science / Geospatial Technologies

University of Washington Tacoma, WA. Sep 2020 – Present (Anticipated Graduation: Aug 2021)

- Cumulative GPA: 4.0 / 4.0
- Upsilon Sigma Honor Society

#### **Bachelor of Arts / Urban Studies**

University of Washington Tacoma, WA. Sep 2013 – Aug 2018

- Cumulative GPA: 3.63 / 4.0
- Tau Sigma Honor Society
- Omicron Delta Kappa Honor Society

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **Marketing Associate**

MERGE HOLDINGS, Seoul, South Korea. / Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

- Worked as a marketing associate at MERGE HOLDINGS, mainly planned and created in-app contents to promote the app uses.
- Managed the information about the local and franchise stores that are in partnership.

#### **Data Curation Associate**

Lyft Corporation, Bellevue, WA. / Dec 2018 - May 2019

- Worked as a data curation associate at Lyft's L5 Autonomous Vehicle OSM mapping team through Ryzen Solutions.
- Used OSM and JOSM to perform highly detailed analysis, edits, and quality control to OSM data.

## **CONTACTS**

Email:

jeminkang1991@gmail.com

**Phone:** 971 380 9278

Address: 3105 S 47th Street,

Tacoma, WA. 98409

# **PORTFOLIO**

#### Wix

https://jkang11.wixsite.com/jeminkang

#### Github

https://jkang11.github.io/By-jkang11/Portfolio/

## **LANGUAGES**

Korean: Native English: Fluent

#### SKILLS

ArcGIS JavaScript

QGIS CSS
OSM HTML

JOSM Python

Microsoft Office

## CERTIFICATE

#### **GIS Certificate**

from University of Washington Tacoma

**Microsoft Office Specialist** from Microsoft Corporation

#### **GIS Intern**

Safe Street Campaign, Tacoma, WA. / Oct 2018 – Nov 2018

- Worked as a GIS intern mainly utilizing GIS software and the U.S. Census data.
- Created multiple thematic maps such as crime report map and socio-economic status map that helped company's decision-making process.

## **Korean Class Instructor**

University of Washington Tacoma, WA. / Mar 2018 – May 2018

- Taught basic Korean to average 15 students.
- Organized and prepared materials for each class.

## VOLUNTEER WORK

#### The Autism Korea

Seoul, South Korea. / Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

- Helped the students understand and focus on the job training session at the Autism center.
- Spent a total of 104 hours as a volunteer.

#### Gonbler

Seoul, South Korea. / Jul 2017 – Sep 2017

- Volunteered as a mentor for students preparing for study abroad.
- Posted useful information related to study in the United States.

#### Sang-II District Children Care

Seoul, South Korea. / Jan 2015 – Mar 2015

- Taught basic English including grammar, speaking, and reading to average of 10 children.
- Spent a total of 20 hours as a volunteer.

# **Military Service**

# Republic of Korea Air Force

Seoul, South Korea. / Jun 2015 – Jun 2017

- Worked with military dog to provide safety for the President of South Korea when he/she visits the airport located in the Seong-Nam Air Force base.
- Detected explosives that can be potential threat to the President of South Korea.
- Trained military dogs for both detecting explosives and guarding the base.